<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Express Entry on Detective Beaver tells stories</title>
    <link>https://detective-beaver.github.io/tags/express-entry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Express Entry on Detective Beaver tells stories</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:42:33 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://detective-beaver.github.io/tags/express-entry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>We have been approved</title>
      <link>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/finally-pr/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Apr 2022 17:42:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/finally-pr/</guid>
      <description>Posting the first post is like reading the first page of a new book. It’s exciting.
What an exciting news: our permanent resident application was approved and now are officially permanent residents!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to obtain Identity History Summary Checks from overseas</title>
      <link>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/american-pcc/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 14 Feb 2021 18:36:51 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/american-pcc/</guid>
      <description>In this post I will share my experience in regards to getting the Police Clearance Certificate (PCC) (USA) while being in Ukraine.
Background Before we dig into details, a bit of background on why we needed to obtain this document.
It was a nice winter day in the middle of February, our application was over 5 months and we had been anxiously waiting for at least any update from the IRCC and you know what it came!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to track your EE application</title>
      <link>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/ee-application-tracking/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 22:00:56 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/ee-application-tracking/</guid>
      <description>John Doe: &amp;ldquo;Today I logged into my EE profile and saw zero changes after 7 months of waiting.&amp;rdquo;
We got you John Doe - it happended to almost each of us. Every year Express Entry applicants come accross the fact that it is almost impossible to understand the real state of their express entry application after it was submitted. Here I&amp;rsquo;ll try to list for your all the useful internet resources that can be handy:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 months after AOR</title>
      <link>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/five-months/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Feb 2021 17:42:33 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://detective-beaver.github.io/posts/five-months/</guid>
      <description>Posting the first post is like reading the first page of a new book. It’s exciting.
It’s been almost 5 months since we submitted our CEC PR application and got AOR. Time flies and it’s definitely giving us a hard time to overcome all the mental challenges of being apart. A family should be together.
Meanwhile, the Canadian Government has been trying to sort out all the bureaucracy to implement a new set of border restrictions due to the COVID pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
